http://www.spiritofadventure.org.nz/privacy-policy

Are you 18 or younger?
Have a love of adventure?
SEACHANGE is a mailing list for young people who might one day step aboard the Spirit of New Zealand. Sign up and you'll find out the real story from onboard the ship.
Name:Email:Date of birth:School:Auckland Leagues Club Inc.Fletcher Building Employee Educational FundHalf Moon Bay MarinaHyundai Motors New Zealand LtdI Ride With Hame (Greg Rieger)Karen FranklinLarry O'neilPorts of Auckland LtdRotary Club of Ashburton PlainsTe Atatu Boating Club IncTennon Clearwood Employee Education TrustNot at schoolACG New Zealand International CollegeACG Parnell CollegeACG Senior CollegeACG Strathallan CollegeACG SunderlandACG TaurangaAhikaa Learning CentreAidanfield Christian SchoolAkaroa Area SchoolAlbany Junior High SchoolAlbany Senior High SchoolAlfriston CollegeAllenvale SchoolAmana Christian SchoolAmbury Park CentreAmuri Area SchoolAo Tawhiti Unlimited DiscoveryAorere CollegeAotea CollegeAparima CollegeAquinas CollegeArahunga Special SchoolArohanui Special SchoolAshburton Christian SchoolAshburton CollegeAuckland Girls Grammar SchoolAuckland Grammar SchoolAuckland International CollegeAuckland Secondary Schools CentreAuckland Seventh Day Adventist High SchoolAurora CollegeAvondale CollegeAvonside Girls High SchoolAwatapu CollegeBaradene CollegeBay of Islands CollegeBay Pathways Alternative EducationBayfield High SchoolBethlehem CollegeBirkenhead CollegeBishop Viard CollegeBLENNZ - NelsonBlue Mountain CollegeBotany Downs Secondary CollegeBream Bay CollegeBroadwood Area SchoolBuller High SchoolBurnside High SchoolCambridge High SchoolCambridge Middle SchoolCampion CollegeCanterbury Christian CollegeCarey CollegeCarmel CollegeCashmere High SchoolCatholic Cathedral CollegeCentral Hawkes Bay CollegeCentral Southland CollegeChanel CollegeChapman CollegeCheviot Area SchoolChilton St. James SchoolChrist's CollegeChristchurch Adventist SchoolChristchurch Boys High SchoolChristchurch Girls High SchoolChristchurch Rudolf Steiner SchoolChristian Renewal SchoolCity Impact Church School (Secondary)Clendon Teen Parent UnitCoastal Taranaki SchoolCollingwood Area SchoolColumba CollegeCornerstone Christian SchoolCoromandel Area SchoolCraighead Diocesan SchoolCromwell CollegeCullinane CollegeDannevirke High SchoolDarfield High SchoolDargaville High SchoolDe La Salle CollegeDestiny SchoolDilworth SchoolDiocesan School for GirlsDrury Christian SchoolDunstan High SchoolEast Otago High SchoolEastern Institute of Technology (E.I.T)Eden CampusEden Christian AcademyEdgecumbe CollegeEdgewater CollegeElim Christian CollegeEllesmere CollegeEmmanuel Christian SchoolEnner Glynn SchoolEpsom Girls Grammar SchoolEvakona EducationExcellere CollegeFairfield CollegeFeilding High SchoolFiordland CollegeFlaxmere CollegeForest View High SchoolFrancis Douglas Memorial CollegeFraser High SchoolFreyberg High SchoolGarin CollegeGeraldine High SchoolGisborne Boys High SchoolGisborne Girls High SchoolGisborne High Schools HostelGlendowie CollegeGlenfield CollegeGloriavale Christian Community SchoolGolden Bay High SchoolGore High SchoolGreen Bay High SchoolGreymouth High SchoolHaeata Community CampusHagley Community CollegeHamilton Boys High SchoolHamilton Christian SchoolHamilton Girls High SchoolHamilton Junior High SchoolHastings Boys High SchoolHastings Christian SchoolHastings Girls High SchoolHato Paora CollegeHato Petera CollegeHauraki Plains CollegeHavelock North High SchoolHawera High SchoolHawke's Bay School for Teenage ParentsHe Huarahi TamarikiHe Mataariki School for Teen ParentsHebron Christian College - AucklandHenderson High SchoolHenderson South Primary SchoolHenderson Teen Parent Unit - He Wero o Nga WahineHeretaunga CollegeHillcrest High SchoolHillmorton High SchoolHillview Christian SchoolHobsonville Point Secondary SchoolHohepa SchoolHome-schooledHornby High SchoolHorowhenua CollegeHowick CollegeHuanui CollegeHukarere Girls CollegeHuntly CollegeHurunui CollegeHutt Independent Boys' SchoolHutt International Boys SchoolHutt Valley High SchoolImmanuel Christian SchoolInglewood High SchoolInternational Language SchoolIona CollegeJames Cook High SchoolJames Hargest CollegeJohn McGlashan CollegeJohn Paul CollegeJohn Paul II High SchoolKadimah Primary SchoolKaiapoi High SchoolKaikohe Christian SchoolKaikorai Valley CollegeKaikoura High SchoolKaipara CollegeKaitaia Abundant Life SchoolKaitaia CollegeKakaramea SchoolKamo High SchoolKapiti CollegeKaramea Area SchoolKaramu High SchoolKaranga Mai Young Parents CollegeKatikati CollegeKavanagh CollegeKawerau CollegeKawhia Primary SchoolKelston Boys High SchoolKelston Girls CollegeKerikeri High SchoolKia Aroha CollegeKimihia Parents' CollegeKing's CollegeKing's High School - DunedinKingslea SchoolKingsway SchoolKorakanui SchoolKristin SchoolKuranui CollegeLake Taupo Christian SchoolLakeland LearningLawrence Area SchoolLevin Teen Parent UnitLincoln High SchoolLindisfarne CollegeLinwood CollegeListon CollegeLiving Way Christian SchoolLogan Park High SchoolLong Bay CollegeLongburn Adventist CollegeLynfield CollegeLytton High SchoolMackenzie CollegeMacleans CollegeMahurangi CollegeMairehau High SchoolMakoura CollegeMana CollegeMana TamarikiManawatu CollegeMangakahia Area SchoolMangakino Area SchoolMangere CollegeManiototo Area SchoolManukau Christian SchoolManukuraManurewa High SchoolMarcellin CollegeMarian CollegeMarist CollegeMarlborough Boys CollegeMarlborough Girls CollegeMassey High SchoolMasterton Intermediate SchoolMatamata CollegeMcAuley High SchoolMelville High SchoolMenzies CollegeMercury Bay Area SchoolMichael Park SchoolMiddle School West AucklandMiddleton Grange SchoolMission Heights Junior CollegeMoerewa SchoolMorrinsville CollegeMotueka High SchoolMotupipi SchoolMount Albert Grammar SchoolMount Aspiring CollegeMount Hobson Middle SchoolMount Hutt CollegeMount Maunganui CollegeMount Richmond Special SchoolMount Roskill Grammar SchoolMountainview High SchoolMurchison Area SchoolMurihiku Young Parents Learning CentreMurupara Area SchoolNaenae CollegeNapier Boys High SchoolNapier Girls High SchoolNayland CollegeNelson CollegeNelson College for GirlsNelson Teen Parent UnitNew Plymouth Boys High SchoolNew Plymouth Girls High SchoolNewlands CollegeNga Taiatea WharekuraNga Tawa Diocesan SchoolNgaruawahia High SchoolNgata Memorial CollegeNorthcote CollegeNorthern Southland CollegeNorthland CollegeNorthland College Teen Parent UnitOdyssey House School - AucklandOkaihau CollegeOne Tree Hill CollegeOnehunga High SchoolOnewhero Area SchoolOnslow CollegeOpihi CollegeOpononi Area SchoolOpotiki CollegeOpunake High SchoolOratia District SchoolOrewa CollegeOrmiston Junior CollegeOrmiston Senior CollegeOtago Boys High SchoolOtago Girls High SchoolOtahuhu CollegeOtaki CollegeOtamatea Christian SchoolOtamatea High SchoolOther InstituteOtorohanga
CollegeOtumoetai CollegeOxford Area SchoolPa Harakeke Teen Parent UnitPacific Advance Senior SchoolPaeroa CollegePakuranga CollegePalmerston North Boys High SchoolPalmerston North Girls High SchoolPapakura High SchoolPapamoa CollegePapanui High SchoolPapatoetoe High SchoolParaparaumu CollegeParoa SchoolPatea Area SchoolPinehurst SchoolPiopio CollegePitt Island SchoolPompallier Catholic CollegePonatahi Christian SchoolPorirua CollegePukeatua SchoolPukekohe Christian SchoolPukekohe High SchoolPukeoware Primary SchoolPutaruru CollegeQueen Charlotte CollegeQueen Elizabeth CollegeQueen Margaret CollegeQueens High SchoolRaglan Area SchoolRai Valley Area SchoolRamarama SchoolRangi Ruru Girls SchoolRangiora High SchoolRangiora New Life SchoolRangitaiki Independent SchoolRangitikei CollegeRangitoto CollegeRaphael House Rudolf Steiner Area SchoolRathkeale CollegeReefton Area SchoolReporoa CollegeRiccarton High SchoolRichmond View Area SchoolRodney CollegeRolleston College Roncalli CollegeRongotai CollegeRosehill CollegeRosmini CollegeRotorua Boys High SchoolRotorua Girls High SchoolRotorua Lakes High SchoolRotorua School for Young ParentsRototuna Junior High SchoolRototuna Senior High SchoolRoxburgh Area SchoolRuapehu CollegeRuawai CollegeRutherford CollegeSacred Heart College - AucklandSacred Heart College - NapierSacred Heart Girls College - HamiltonSacred Heart Girls College - Lower HuttSacred Heart Girls College - New PlymouthSamuel Marsden Collegiate School - KaroriSamuel Marsden Collegiate School - WhitbySancta Maria CollegeScots CollegeSelwyn CollegeSeven Oaks Secondary SchoolShirley Boys High SchoolSilverstream Christian SchoolSir Edmund Hillary Collegiate - Senior SchoolSolway CollegeSonrise Christian SchoolSouth Auckland Middle SchoolSouth Otago High SchoolSouth Westland Area SchoolSouthern Cross CampusSouthland Boys High SchoolSouthland Girls High SchoolSpotswood CollegeSpringbank SchoolSt Andrew's CollegeSt Bede's CollegeSt Bernard's CollegeSt Catherine's CollegeSt Cuthbert's CollegeSt Dominic's Catholic College - HendersonSt Dominic's College - WhanganuiSt Hilda's Collegiate SchoolSt John's College - HamiltonSt John's College - HastingsSt Joseph's Maori Girls CollegeSt Kentigern CollegeSt Kevin's CollegeSt Margaret's CollegeSt Mary's College - AucklandSt Mary's College - WellingtonSt Mary's Diocesan School for Girls - StratfordSt Matthew's Collegiate SchoolSt Oran's CollegeSt Patrick's College - SilverstreamSt Patrick's College - WellingtonSt Paul's College
- AucklandSt Paul's Collegiate School - HamiltonSt Peter's College - AucklandSt Peter's College - GoreSt Peter's College - Palmerston NorthSt Peter's School - CambridgeSt Thomas of Canterbury CollegeStratford High SchoolStratford High School Teen Parent UnitTai Wananga Ki RuakuraTaieri CollegeTaihape Area SchoolTaikura Rudolf Steiner SchoolTaipa Area SchoolTaita CollegeTakapuna Grammar SchoolTamaki CollegeTamatea High SchoolTangaroa CollegeTangaroa College Teen Parent UnitTapawera Area SchoolTaradale High SchoolTararua CollegeTarawera High SchoolTauhara CollegeTaumarunui High SchoolTaupo-Nui-A-Tia CollegeTauranga Boys CollegeTauranga Girls CollegeTauraroa Area SchoolTawa CollegeTe Aho Te Kura Pounamu (Correspondence School)Te Ara (Wellington Activties Centre)Te Aratika AcademyTe Aroha CollegeTe Aute CollegeTe Awamutu CollegeTe Karaka Area SchoolTe Kauwhata CollegeTe KKM o Puau Te Moananui-a-KiwaTe Kuiti High SchoolTe Kura Hourua o Whangarei Terenga ParaoaTe Kura Kaupapa Maori o Horouta WanangaTe Kura Mana Maori o WhangaparaoaTe Kura Maori o Nga TapuwaeTe Kura Maori o PoriruaTe Kura Maori-a-Rohe o WaiohauTe Kura o HirangiTe Kura o KokohuiaTe Kura o Nga Ruahine RangiTe Kura Taumata o PanguruTe Kura Toitu o Te Whaiti-nui-a-ToiTe Kura-a-iwi o Whakatupuranga Rua ManoTe Pa o RakaihautuTe Pi'ipi'inga Kakano Mai RangiateaTe Puke High SchoolTe Pumanawa O Te WairuaTe Rangi AniwaniwaTe Tipu Whenua o Pa HarakekeTe Waha O Rerekohu Area SchoolTe Whakatipuranga - Otumoetai TPUTe Whanau-A-Apanui area SchoolTe Whare Whai Hua Teenage Parent CentreTe Wharekura o ArowhenuaTe Wharekura o ManaiaTe Wharekura o ManiapotoTe Wharekura o ManurewaTe Wharekura o MauaoTe Wharekura o Nga Purapura o Te ArohaTe Wharekura o RakaumangamangaTe Wharekura o RuatokiTe Wharekura o Te Kaokaoroa o PatetereTe Wharekura o Te Rau ArohaTe Whata Tau o PutauakiThames High SchoolThe Bridge AcademyThe Catlins Area SchoolThe Corelli SchoolTikipunga High SchoolTimaru Boys High SchoolTimaru Christian SchoolTimaru Girls' High SchoolTitirangi Rudolph Steiner SchoolTitiro WhakamuaTKK Motuhake o TawhiuauTKK o Te Wananga Whare Tapere o TakitimuTKKM o Hoani WaititiTKKM o HuiarauTKKM o KaikoheTKKM o Kawakawa mai TawhitiTKKM o MangereTKKM o Nga MokopunaTKKM o Nga Uri A MauiTKKM o Ngati Kahungunu Ki HeretaungaTKKM o Ngati Kahungunu o Te WairoaTKKM o PukemiroTKKM o RuamataTKKM o Tamaki Nui A RuaTKKM o TaumarereTKKM o Te Ara HouTKKM o Te Ara WhanuiTKKM o Te KoutuTKKM o Te Kura KokiriTKKM o Te Raki PaewhenuaTKKM o Te Rawhiti RoaTKKM o Te RitoTKKM o Te Tonga o HokiangaTKKM o Te Waiu o Ngati PorouTKKM o Te Whanau TahiTKKM o Tuia te MatangiTKKM o TupohoTKKM o WairarapaTKKM o WaitahaTKKM o Whakarewa I Te Reo Ki TuwharetoaTKKM o WhangaroaTokomairiro High SchoolTokoroa High SchoolTolaga Bay Area SchoolTongariro SchoolTotara College of Accelerated LearningTrident High SchoolTuakau CollegeTurakina Maori Girls CollegeTwizel Area SchoolTyndale Park Christian SchoolUnlimited SchoolUpper Hutt CollegeUpper Moutere SchoolVanguard Military SchoolVerdon CollegeVilla Maria CollegeWa Ora Montessori CollegeWaiau Area SchoolWaiheke High SchoolWaihi CollegeWaikato Diocesan School for GirlsWaikato Waldorf School - Rudolf SteinerWaimate High SchoolWaimea CollegeWainuiomata High SchoolWaiopehu CollegeWairarapa CollegeWairarapa Teen Parent UnitWairoa CollegeWaitakere CollegeWaitaki Boys High SchoolWaitaki Girls High SchoolWaitara High SchoolWaiuku CollegeWakatipu High SchoolWanganui Collegiate SchoolWellington CollegeWellington East Girls CollegeWellington Girls CollegeWellington High SchoolWentworth CollegeWesley CollegeWestern Heights High SchoolWestern Springs CollegeWestlake Boys High SchoolWestlake Girls High SchoolWestland High SchoolWestmount SchoolWhakatane High SchoolWhakatipuria Teen Parent UnitWhangamata Area SchoolWhanganui City CollegeWhanganui Girls CollegeWhanganui High SchoolWhangaparaoa CollegeWhangarei Boys High SchoolWhangarei Girls High SchoolWhangaroa CollegeWilliam Colenso CollegeWoodford HouseZayed College for GirlsGender:
Thanks for subscribing!
Look out for cool things in your inbox!
Or follow us
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
Youtube
git ad
Book now
Donate
Shop
0800 472 454
Seachange
Will you be next?
Privacy Policy
Spirit of Adventure Trust Privacy Protocols
General Statement
This sets out Spirit of Adventure Trust (SoAT) policies and procedures for the collection, use, retention and disclosure of personal information we hold about participants, friends and family, donors, supporters, clients, partners, contractors, employees and prospective employees, volunteers, other individuals we deal with in the course of carrying on our business, and all other individuals we deal with who come into contact with us. It is intended to be a resource for SoAT staff.
We value your privacy. We will never give, lease, sell, or otherwise disclose your personal information. Any information given to SoAT will be held with the utmost care. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions at all about our privacy or the storage of your information please contact either the General Manager or CEO of the Spirit of Adventure Trust.
Storage of Information
This policy is to ensure that people who connect with SoAT and are asked to or provide personal information, are assured that this information is gathered in line with the Privacy Act and its principles.
SoAT will gather, store and release personal information in line with the 12 Privacy Principles of the Privacy Act.
Types of Information collected
SoAT collects non-personally identifiable information via Google Analytics and personally identifiable information from our online forms.
Non-personally identifiable information might include your IP address, your browser type or operating system, the domain name from which you linked to our site, your city, and other general demographic information. We use this information to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We may share it with our affiliates or business partners at an aggregated level.
Personally, identifiable information from our merchandise transactions and donation, registration, contact, booking, and survey forms could include your name, telephone number, home address and e-mail address. We may use this information to contact you (you can opt-out of receiving future information from us). We will keep your personal information confidential, in accordance with the Privacy Act (1993), for the purposes of SoAT Voyages, administration, and promotional activities.
Resale or Disclosure of Information to Third Parties
Spirit of Adventure Trust does not sell, rent, loan, trade or lease any personal information collected by our website, including contact forms, download requests or email lists.
Usage Information Collected By Our Website
SoAT does collect information about how people are using our website in order to improve the value of our website and the materials available on the website
Unsubscribe
We strive to only send email to those who want to receive it. If you do not want to receive future emails from us, please use the “unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of our email communications or advise us to remove you from our email list.
Privacy of our Email Lists
Individuals join our mailing lists and are added to our database using the forms provided on this website. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade or lease the addresses on our lists to anyone. In addition, we configure our email software to refuse to divulge the email addresses of our list subscribers to anyone but authorised Spirit of Adventure Trust Staff, including other list subscribers.
Email Communications
Email communications to and from you to SoAT Staff emails addresses are company information, are retained on the SoAT companies email server and can be reviewed by approved staff where there is a need to verify or confirm information supplied or provided.
Credit card details
If you pay for items on our site using a Credit Card, your card details are not stored by us and cannot be used by our staff. Our shop uses a secure transaction system.
Resale or Disclosure of Information to Third Parties
SoAT does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected by our website, including contact forms, download requests or email lists.
CCTV
For security reasons, some areas of the SoAT Operation have or could have CCTV in operation. The video files are only accessed for legal and security reasons. If required the CEO or other designated staff may review these and should there be a legal reason, then the video or pictures can be are released to relevant authorities in order for them to complete their investigations.
Promotional Material
Once you have booked on a SoAT Voyage, you authorise SoAT the right to use your name, comments and images obtained in relation to your Voyage / SoAT participation, and to disclose this information to third parties for promotional purposes; these materials will remain the property of SoAT.
You grant SoAT permission to contact you by email, including a regular e-newsletter and other updates.
Medical Information
If you intend to undertake a voyage with the SoAT, we will need you to supply your background medical information, details of medications you may be on and other relevant information to ensure it is safe and suitable for you to participate. We will also require emergency contact details in case of a medical emergency along with your consent to allow the approved SoAT staff member to discuss your medical condition with the emergency contacts.
Your medical information is held securely and is only available to selected SoAT staff who need to be aware of your medical background for your well-being and safety.
Storage of Records
Where information is of a sensitive nature, such as medical records, then this information will be stored if in hard copy in a locked cabinet with controlled access, or if electronic, on password protected files, only accessible by approved staff.
Police Vetting
All SoAT personnel, are required to undergo Police Vetting. The Police report will only be viewed by the Executive Management Team. The report will be held on the individual’s personnel files. Personnel files are held under secure storage.
Phone Conversations
SoAT does have the ability to record conversations on the phone. This is only done when the content of the call may be needed to be retained for future reference and confirmation of information. Callers shall be advised before the recording is activated. Callers can request a copy of the recording.
Back to top
